I'm late! I'm late! I'm late! I'm late!
I can't get my eyebrows right!
What?
I can't!
Can you move over a little bit?
Sonata, you're in the way!
No, you are!
Come, Lily, if you wash your faces too much, it'll get even plainer!
Stop! Don't call me plain!
The Buddha's beating me!
Hey, shut up!
Son Paul, the breakfast is amazing again this morning!
Pack it!
Me too!
You've all settled in nicely!
Tokamira-san!
Good morning!
Make sure you eat a good breakfast, ladies!
Okay!
It's empty.
More food.
Sorry.
Everyone eats so much!
You see?
I've still only had fried helpings.
That's not nearly enough.
You're absolutely right!
I will go make some more cream right now!
It's been a month since we came to Akibastar and started living together as trainees.
It's only been a short while, but we've already developed customs of sorts.
No running.
It's a walking race.
Okay!
After we finish breakfast, we head to the dorm's lesson room.
Ushiyama-sensei says the best position is behind him diagonally.
So in order to secure the best position, everyone tries to get there first.
Good morning!
Ushiyama-sensei's not here.
Where is he?
What are you doing?
Tsubasa-san.
There's no lesson.
Today's your monthly day off.
Not just for you, but for the successors as well.
What?
Come to think of it.
I had completely forgotten.
Well, let's practice on our own then!
Good idea!
I know, right?
Oh yeah, definitely!
Are you sure about that?
Zero-Zero always keeps a strict schedule.
It's important to use your time well.
Your ability to spend your time off meaningfully will determine your futures here.
Ready and…
Let's go!
AKB-0048!
societies will play with me at home with a giant penguin setting!
Man Dosuckалы who are the Relaxing Professor, and he is watching a little
ASU 가장 good look up!
Be confident, you will leave a little longê!
We've all got slack in our class area, but keep a strict schedule.
It is important to use your time well.
Your ability to spend your time off meaningfully will determine your future here.
Ready and…
AKB-0048!
Even if I take my hand, I can't reach now.
My dreams will be far too far.
If I take my hand, I can't reach now.
I can't reach now.
If you are with your eyes, I can't reach now.
So yeah, today is a meaningful day off.
Chiri?
Where are you going?
Shopping.
What?
What are you going to buy?
I can spend my day off however I want.
Chiri?
She's running off by herself, huh?
By herself?
Nagisa!
Why does she bother with her?
Makoto, I think you need to come along with me.
What?
What do you want?
It's something good.
Huh?
What?
Hey Linda, come with me.
Don't you want to go with Kanata-san?
She is your sister.
There's something around here I've always wanted to do.
Huh?
Sana-ti, you're wild.
Ah!
Well, usually...
Donkey, donkey...
Ah!
The bath isn't a playground.
My sister always gets mad at me.
Just once, I've wanted to play in this bath.
I suppose such elegant bathing is quite precious to some.
Hey, is there something anything you want to do, Linda?
I've been thinking about Zero Zero's operation.
Operation?
Mm-hmm.
Since coming to Akibastar, there have been plenty of staff members helping us out.
But...
There should be an individual who makes all of Zero Zero's decisions.
What?
Sensei-sensei.
My Yu-yu-san?
When did you get here?
Um...
Who is Sensei-sensei?
My seconds are in there.
My rice.
Hey!
Stop!
Seconds.
My rice.
I've been thinking about this.
You need to start building up stamina.
Give me a break.
If I end up weirdly muscular.
You know.
As an idol.
I...
Hey, ripped legs!
Huh?
Koji-hara-san?
Ripped legs!
Eh?
Kanata's ripped legs!
R...
Ripped legs?
What do you mean?
The way Nyan-nan sees it, the two of you don't have enough pheromones.
I have enough pheromones! I can help you with that!
Pheromones?
Nyan will train you!
I called it Nyan Nyan's pheromone increasing plan!
Come on! Let's go!
Wait! Kuchiharo! Wait!
Pheromones? How wonderful!
I'd love to join in!
Memori, you're already excreting too many pheromones.
There, there, Sayaka!
What? You think so?
Who are you, Tomami?
I can't watch this. Come on, Say. Grab that arm.
Okay, okay.
An idol should be fresh instead of erotic.
I call it my pheromone reducing plan.
Reducing?
What was that scream?
It was kinda... scary.
Oh, come on, girls. You know you don't have to help me on your day off.
Oh, it's fine. You always cook for us.
I appreciate the help, but...
You should take a break too, Chef Lapa.
Let us handle this for you, okay?
Are you sure?
Oh, in that case, maybe I'll go check out those fancy new rice cookers.
See you later!
Ta-ta!
Nagisa should have helped us too.
Why does she care about Chieri so much?
Are you jealous?
You idiot! That's not it! Not at all!
Tomochin-san!
Is breakfast today over already?
Oh, um, Chef Papa went out.
Feed me something!
I could make you some fried rice.
Thanks for the food.
Tabasco sauce, chili oil, and more.
Tomochin-san is kind of mysterious.
Hey.
Uh, yeah?
Do you have any plans?
After this?
Uh...
Thank you very much. Come again.
Chieri.
I wonder if her family situation is alright.
How long are you going to keep following me?
Oh, well, I...
Excuse me!
Huh?
Chieri!
What?
Watch out!
Run! Come on!
We gotta hurry up!
Why would I run?
Besides, I can't run with you on top of me now, can I?
Wha...
What do you want with us, huh?
Uh, I don't mean to be rude, but the price tag's still on your skirt.
I thought you might want to remove it, you know?
What?
I'm very sorry if we were rude.
So, um, if there's anything bothering you or you're worried about something, I want you to tell me about it.
Where did that come from?
I don't know.
I just wish you'd open your heart to me a little more. That's all.
I just love you anyway...
Yuko-san!
Poor S's.
Sensei-sensei.
You, Kirin-san!
You shouldn't do that.
Huh?
I know it's very tempting in all girls,
but even the successors are forbidden
from researching S quadruple.
Forbidden?
What happens to someone if they break that rule?
Hmm...
If you break it...
they'll take...
your belly button.
Belly button?
S quadruple.
My belly button.
Huh?
It's Tsubasa.
What?
Sensei-sensei did?
I understand.
I'll be right there.
Sensei-sensei.
What?
As a Zero Zero fan,
I can't turn back now.
Let's go, Sana-ti.
Huh?
I don't want to!
I think my belly button might actually be pretty important!
I took a bath with you.
No!
No, my belly button!
Sorry for making you help me.
Oh, don't worry about it.
It's okay.
Here.
What?!
Oh, it's amazing!
This yard!
It's like a park!
Tomomi, welcome home.
Oh, and are you young ladies the new trainees?
Yeah.
Excuse the intrusion!
Her mother's beautiful!
She looks just like Tomo-chin-san!
Oh, trainees!
Oh, you must be the 77th generation.
My, how adorable!
So many Tomo-chin-sans!
Oh!
Amazing!
Generations of Tomo-chin-sans!
They all look alike!
Our family!
Oh!
They all look alike!
Our family has succeeded Tomomi Itano for generations.
Huh?
Tomomi Itano for generations?
Oh!
It is not important for successors to appear physically similar to the original.
However, because our family carries the genes of the original Tomo-chin,
we train ourselves to be as close to the original as possible...
And of course...
Tomomi!
Welcome home.
Dad.
Make yourselves at home, trainees.
Thank you very much.
In order to look like her,
we even chose husbands who look like Tomo-chin.
Really?
Yeah.
You seem to be carrying them with you.
Are those scrolls?
Is that what was in there?
There are 48 Tomo-chin scrolls in total.
Do you want to see your reward for helping me?
Yeah.
Those of Tomo-chin must maintain a high sense of beauty.
Those of Tomo-chin must always have a poor sense of taste.
Oh, I see.
No!
Turn your toes in more!
Okay.
Uh-oh.
Word up, my home skillet!
Bemori.
Oh, I can't!
My chest feels too tight!
My neck feels so hot!
Hey!
You're releasing pheromones again!
All my hard work for nothing.
You still need more training!
Let's run 10 more laps around the door!
Sorry for interrupting.
Pheromones, huh?
Do you think that losing them is harder than gaining them?
Uh...
Hmm...
I think that's a special case.
This one of Takamina-san is cute.
She's making kind of a weird face, though.
I know, right?
And this one of Yukiren-san.
Yeah!
I love cameras.
I always take pictures of the other members during breaks in our days off.
That's surprising.
Huh?
What is?
You seem like you'd play sports on your days off, that's all.
Nope, I'm actually really into photography.
I also like reading and puzzles.
I'm really playing.
Uh, Kirara?
That's the...
previous Aachan.
The previous Aachan was wonderful.
She was usually quiet and reserved,
but once she got on stage,
all the Kiaras gathered around her and shone.
It was like Aachan was wearing a dress made of light.
I was still a trainee back then,
and that's when I decided
I wanted to sing side-by-side with Aachan someday.
But as soon as I became a successor,
she left for good.
She left?
All the members who become Center Novas end up quitting mysteriously.
What?
I've heard that...
Aachan disappeared in the middle of a concert.
Disappeared?
I was part of the team that stayed on Akibaster during the concert.
So, I really don't know what happened.
People say she might have run away or been kidnapped.
That can't be true.
It's not just Aachan.
All the past Center Novas,
Michon,
Yui-Han,
Tomomi,
and all the others have disappeared.
But some people don't want to make their reasons for graduating publicly known.
And some people say they've seen Michon around here.
In order to prevent the rumors from growing anymore,
they discontinued the Center Nova position after the previous Aachan.
So that's the reason.
But I can't accept that!
No way!
I looked up to the previous Aachan.
I've been working hard to become a Center Nova who exceeds Aachan!
Hmm.
I suppose I've worked since the day I was bored to become Tomo-chin.
But sometimes I imagine what it would be like to live life as someone differently,
other than Tomo-chin.
Tomo-chin-san!
Koji-haru.
But I like
that I'm on stage as Tomo-chin.
It actually took me a pretty long time to accomplish my goals.
Becoming the eighth generation Koji-haru was difficult.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I was the same generation as Yuko.
She became a successor before me,
so I kinda panicked.
We all have our strengths and weaknesses,
but we're a team!
Everyone's unique in their own way,
but I think it's good to try different things.
Try?
Zero-Zero is a weird place.
Working so hard to become someone who isn't yourself?
Funny.
But the reason we can work so hard is because we have friends.
Right, Memoria-san?
We're friends then?
Yep.
The closest of them were friends of the heart.
Because we have friends running in the same place,
carrying the same feelings.
That's why we can work so hard.
We can always look up to them!
Well, I'm gonna go take some more photos in the area before I head home.
Take care!
You know something?
I wanna be Yuko-san.
What?
I want to succeed Yuko-san!
Are you saying you want Yuko-san to graduate?
Two girls can't succeed the same member at the same time.
Oh, you're right.
I don't want Yuko-san to leave or anything.
You must like Yuko-san too, Chiri.
Yuko-san's dancing is...
It's so dynamic.
I just wish I could dance like her.
I hope I will someday.
Me too.
Could S-Quadruple be...
Ushiyama-sensei?
I'm just an idiot.
I knew there was no way that I could trust a man like him, but I did.
Love is just so excitable, you know?
I'm a woman.
I can't help it.
Aren't you a man?
Bite your tongue.
I'm saying I have the heart of a woman.
It seems unlikely if you stop to think.
Linda, Linda!
Look!
It's a kitty!
Meow!
Sana-ti, you and the kitty need to be quiet.
Isn't it like this?
No.
But this is how Yuko-san danced at the last concert.
I remember it.
No, no.
The steps were bigger.
What?
Huh?
When did this happen?
I'm sorry.
We're not street performers or anything.
We just, uh, got excited while talking about the way our senior danced.
But when we actually tried it, we felt like something was off and got so focused that...
I'm really sorry.
This is harder than I thought.
I feel like my mouth is cramping.
Really?
It's actually not that hard at all.
It's impossible.
Sexy!
Taxi!
I feel like I'm starting to emit some pheromones.
I've actually been feeling pretty sexy for a while now.
Really?
Alright!
Let's get even sexier!
Okay!
Hey!
What's wrong, Memori?
Are you done already?
No, I can't keep going!
Memori-san, fight!
Anyway...
You're such a boring woman.
Oh.
You're drinking water instead of liquor.
I was planning to go see Sensei-Sensei after this, but...
You know.
Huh.
Hey, Chiyori.
When we get back to the dorm, do you want to practice Yuko-san's steps together?
Sure.
I'll show you just how wrong you are.
I'll show you!
I'll take these girls home.
I wonder if they properly enjoyed this priceless day off.
Taking care of children is tough...
Margo-sama.
No.
Lifeers who mean the dream in life Now we go extinct.
ひとは生まれて人は死んでゆく肉体は滅びるよ
灰の中から蘇るものは情熱
Deja Vuのような 遠い記憶
まるでリンカーネーション
今もまた 無意識のうちに
どこかへ走ってる
いくつ目の涙で 諦めるのか
いくつ目の命で 叶うものなのか
ご視聴ありがとうございました